// All the questions in the quiz

let data = [
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Hydrogen",
                answer:1
            },{
                question:" Hydrogen's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Gas"
            },
            {
                question:"Hydrogen's abbreviation",
                answer:"H"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Helium",
                answer:2
            },{
                question:" Helium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Gas"
            },
            {
                question:"Helium's abbreviation",
                answer:"He"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Lithium",
                answer:3
            },{
                question:"Lithium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Lithium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Li"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Beryllium",
                answer:4
            },{
                question:"Beryllium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Beryllium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Be"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Boron",
                answer:5
            },{
                question:"Boron's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Boron's abbreviation",
                answer:"B"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Carbon",
                answer:6
            },{
                question:"Carbon's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Carbon's abbreviation",
                answer:"C"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Nitrogen",
                answer:7
            },{
                question:"Nitrogen's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Gas"
            },
            {
                question:"Nitrogen's abbreviation",
                answer:"N"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Oxygen",
                answer:8
            },{
                question:"Oxygen's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Gas"
            },
            {
                question:"Oxygen's abbreviation",
                answer:"O"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Fluorine",
                answer:9
            },{
                question:"Fluorine's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Gas"
            },
            {
                question:"Fluorine's abbreviation",
                answer:"F"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Neon",
                answer:10
            },{
                question:"Neon's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Gas"
            },
            {
                question:"Neon's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ne"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Sodium",
                answer:11
            },{
                question:"Sodium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Sodium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Na"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Magnesium                ",
                answer:12
            },{
                question:"Magnesium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Magnesium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Mg"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Aluminium            ",
                answer:13
            },{
                question:"Aluminium 's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Aluminium 's abbreviation",
                answer:"Al"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Silicon          ",
                answer:14
            },{
                question:"Silicon 's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Silicon 's abbreviation",
                answer:"Si"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Phosphorus  ",
                answer:15
            },{
                question:"Phosphorus 's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Phosphorus 's abbreviation",
                answer:"P"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Sulfur  ",
                answer:16
            },{
                question:"Sulfur 's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Sulfur's abbreviation",
                answer:"S"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Chlorine  ",
                answer:17
            },{
                question:"Chlorine 's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Gas"
            },
            {
                question:"Chlorine's abbreviation",
                answer:"Cl"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Argon  ",
                answer:18
            },{
                question:"Argon's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Gas"
            },
            {
                question:"Argon's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ar"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Potassium ",
                answer:19
            },{
                question:"Potssium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Potassium's abbreviation",
                answer:"K"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Calium ",
                answer:20
            },{
                question:"Calium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Calium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ca"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Scandium",
                answer:21
            },{
                question:"Scandium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Scandium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Sc"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Titanium",
                answer:22
            },{
                question:"Titanium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Titanium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ti"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Vandium",
                answer:23
            },{
                question:"Vandium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Vandium's abbreviation",
                answer:"V"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Chromium",
                answer:24
            },{
                question:"Chromium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Chromium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Cr"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Manganese",
                answer:25
            },{
                question:"Manganese's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Manganese's abbreviation",
                answer:"Mn"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Iron",
                answer:26
            },{
                question:"Iron's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Iron's abbreviation",
                answer:"Fe"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Colbat",
                answer:27
            },{
                question:"Colbat's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Colbat's abbreviation",
                answer:"Co"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Nickel",
                answer:28
            },{
                question:"Nickel's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Nickel's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ni"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Copper",
                answer:29
            },{
                question:"Copper's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Copper's abbreviation",
                answer:"Cu"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Zinc",
                answer:30
            },{
                question:"Zinc's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Zinc's abbreviation",
                answer:"Zn"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Gallium",
                answer:31
            },{
                question:"Gallium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Gallium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ga"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Germanium",
                answer:32
            },{
                question:"Germanium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Germanium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ge"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Arsenic",
                answer:33
            },{
                question:"Arsenic's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Arsenic's abbreviation",
                answer:"As"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Selenium",
                answer:34
            },{
                question:"Selenium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Selenium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Se"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Bromine",
                answer:35
            },{
                question:"Bromine's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Liquid"
            },
            {
                question:"Bromine's abbreviation",
                answer:"Br"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Krypton",
                answer:36
            },{
                question:"Krypton's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Liquid"
            },
            {
                question:"Krypton's abbreviation",
                answer:"Kr"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Rubidium",
                answer:37
            },{
                question:"Rubidium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Rubidium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Rb"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Strontium",
                answer:37
            },{
                question:"Strontium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Strontium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Sr"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Yttrium",
                answer:39
            },{
                question:"Yttrium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Yttrium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Y"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Zirconium",
                answer:40
            },{
                question:"Zirconium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Zirconium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Zr"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Niobium",
                answer:41
            },{
                question:"Niobium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Niobium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Nb"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Molybdenum",
                answer:42
            },{
                question:"Molybdenum's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Molybdenum's abbreviation",
                answer:"Mo"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Technetium",
                answer:43
            },{
                question:"Technetium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Technetium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Tc"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Ruthenium",
                answer:44
            },{
                question:"Ruthenium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Ruthenium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ru"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Rhodium",
                answer:45
            },{
                question:"Rhodium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Rhodium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Rh"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Palladium",
                answer:46
            },{
                question:"Palladium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Palladium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Pd"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Silver",
                answer:47
            },{
                question:"Silver's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Silver's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ag"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Cadmium",
                answer:48
            },{
                question:"Cadmium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Cadmium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Cd"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Indium",
                answer:49
            },{
                question:"Indium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Indium's abbreviation",
                answer:"In"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of protons in Tin",
                answer:50
            },{
                question:"Tin's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Tin's abbreviation",
                answer:"Sn"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Antimony",
                answer:51
            },{
                question:"Antimony's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Antimony's abbreviation",
                answer:"Sb"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Tellurium",
                answer:52
            },{
                question:"Tellurium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Tellurium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Te"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Iodine",
                answer:53
            },{
                question:"Iodine's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Iodine's abbreviation",
                answer:"I"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Xneon",
                answer:54
            },{
                question:"Xneon's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Xneon's abbreviation",
                answer:"Xe"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Caesium",
                answer:55
            },{
                question:"Caesium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Caesium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Cs"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Barium",
                answer:56
            },{
                question:"Barium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Barium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ba"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Lanthanum",
                answer:57
            },{
                question:"Lanthanum's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Lanthanum's abbreviation",
                answer:"La"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Cerium",
                answer:58
            },{
                question:"Cerium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Cerium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Ce"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Praseodymium",
                answer:59
            },{
                question:"Praseodymium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Praseodymium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Pr"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Neodymium",
                answer:60
            },{
                question:"Neodymium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Neodymium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Nd"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Promethium",
                answer:61
            },{
                question:"Promethium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Promethium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Pm"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Samarium",
                answer:62
            },{
                question:"Samarium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Samarium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Sm"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        points:0,
        questionAndPoints: [
            {
                question:"Number of electrons in Europium",
                answer:63
            },{
                question:"Europium's State at room temperature",
                answer:"Solid"
            },
            {
                question:"Europium's abbreviation",
                answer:"Eu"
            }
        ]
    },
]